

Personal

Name Hakan Karadeniz

Address Gaziosmanpaşa 34240 İstanbul

Phone number +90 531 392 1672

Fmail

hakan.karadeniz@outlook.com

Gender Male

Driving licence

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hakan-karadeniz-644880180/

Interests

Playing Piano
Body Building
Playing Football
Bilgi Robotics Student Club

Languages

Turkish Native English B2

Hakan Karadeniz

I completed my 4 years education year at the Department of Electrical and Electronics Engineering at Istanbul Bilgi University. I want to implement and manage national and international projects that touch people's lives in a company where I can use my experience, demonstrate my technical knowledge and skills, and be useful. In line with this goal, I continue to improve myself with the principle of life long learning.

Education and Qualifications

Electrical and Electronics Engineering

Oct 2017 - Present

Istanbul Bilgi University, Istanbul

Business / Faculty of Open and Distance Education

Oct 2020 - Present

Istanbul University

Work experience

Software Development Intern

Apr 2022 - Jul 2022

Nettsi Informatics Technology, Istanbul, Turkey

- -Using command screen with Linux and mostly used commands.
- -Object Orianted Programming with C++, Standart Template Library, VSCode extensions.
- -I observed very clearly how important it is to work as a team and why the SCRUM is so important.
- -Basic knowledge about TCP/UDP protocols, OSI Layers, WireShark.
- -Using Git commands

Working Student in University

Jul 2021 - Aug 2021

Istanbul Bilgi University, Istanbul/Eyüpsultan

- -Teamwork and process management
- -Ability to speak and express oneself in public

Electrical & Electronics Engineer Intern

Sep 2020 - Oct 2020

YAMAS A.Ş., Bursa/Nlüfer

- -Project management
- -Team work

Skills

Linux (Ubuntu) C/C++ Python C#

Java

Github

https://github.com/hakankaradeniz

References

Ümit Koç (Mentor)

Nettsi Informatics Technology

+90 538 433 75 37 umitkoc.com@gmail.com